danteporn.com 2014-06-19

# Magnus Privacy Statement

We have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal and non-personal information provided by visitors to our Web site. By using this site, you signify your assent to our privacy practices and the terms and conditions of our Web site. 

If this policy is not agreeable to you, please do not use this site.

WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?  
Personal Information  
We only collect personal information from visitors to our Web site when they voluntarily provide it to us by completing our registration form or electing to use one of our services. This Site collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database. 

If the Site features or conducts any special events, special promotions or offers, contests or polls, a Member of the Site may be asked to provide information in order to participate, if the Member voluntarily provides that information, all such information may be collected by the Site and included in its customer database. 

Non-Personal Information  
When visitors access our Web site, certain non-personal information may be collected from them including, but not limited to, their browser type (e.g., Netscape or Internet Explorer), operating system (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), IP address, and the domain name from which they accessed the site (e.g., lycos.com). In addition, we may collect information about visitors' browsing behavior, such as the date and time they visit the Web site and the areas or pages of our Web site that they visit. We do not track any information about visitors once they leave our site. We may use cookies (small text files that are stored on visitors computers when they access our Web site) to collect this information. Information collected through cookies may be combined with visitors' personal information. Visitors are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so they may not be able to use certain features on our Web site. The "help" segment of the toolbar on most browsers explains how to configure a browser to not accept new cookies, how to have the browser inform a user when they receive a new cookie, and how to erase cookies from their hard drives. 

IN WHAT WAY DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
Our goal in collecting personal information is to provide visitors with the most personalized Web experience possible and our advertisers with an efficient means to reach the right audience. By knowing a little about our visitors, we are able to deliver more relevant content and advertisements, and provide better services. By the Member's use of the Site, the Member expressly agrees that the Site may use any personal information that has been provided by the Member or that has been collected by the Site about the Member for any purpose, including without limitation, technical, administration, research and development, customer administration, marketing, trading in Personal Data, age verification, promotional and advertising use by the Site or third parties authorized to use the information by the Site. By the Member's use of the Site, the Member expressly agrees that the Site may, in its sole discretion share, disclose, transfer, rent, license or sell any of the personal information about Members that it has gathered or collected with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties. 

SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE SITE.  
Consistent with the Policies set forth in this Privacy Statement, the Site has adopted and implemented reasonable and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to Members that is collected by the Site. All Members should consider any information provided to or collected by the Site as non-confidential, and consequently the Site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any Member is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient. 

"OPT-IN" and "OPT-OUT" Provisions.  
There may be occasions when a Member will be presented with special offers either from the operators of the Site or from third-party service or content providers, which may include consent to receive e-mail solicitations, communications, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other promotional or special event materials (collectively referred to as "Offers"). 

"OPT-IN" -- Some Offers may be presented to the Member with the option to express the subsciber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes" the Member indicates that the Member "OPTS-IN" to that Offer and thereby agrees and assents that the Member's personal information and data may be disclosed to third-parties. 

"OPT-OUT" -- Other Offers may be presented with a pre-selected preference or choice. If the Member does not deselect the pre-selected preference of choice (i.e. "OPT-OUT" of the Offer) then the Site may transfer the Member's personal profile information to the third-party service or content provider making the Offer. If the Member deselects the pre-selected preference then no personal information about the Member may be disclosed to the third-party service or content provider associated with that specific offer. 

"OPT-OUT" Revocation Procedure.   
The Site also offers all Members a procedure for "Opting-Out" if the Member subsequently chooses to revoke any consent to receive Offers by sending an e-mail to webmaster@magnusbucks.com, clearly stating that the Member has revoked consent to receive any future Offers. 

CORPORATE CHANGES  
In the event of a merger, acquisition, asset or stock sale, bankruptcy, or other asset transfer (regardless of legal formality), any of our assets may be transferred to a third party, including personal information collected from visitors to our Web site. 

ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY TERMS & CONDITIONS  
By visiting this Web site, you are agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. By visiting this site, you also accept, without limitation or qualification, all terms and conditions concerning the use of this site. We may at any time revise these terms and conditions. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current terms and conditions to which you are bound. To the extent that any of the third-party sites accessible through our Web site (such as our advertisers) have different privacy practices from those stated in this Privacy Policy, those third-party privacy practices govern the collection and use of information you provide when visiting those sites. We are not responsible for the policies, content, and practices of other companies. 

WE PROTECT CHILDREN'S PRIVACY  
Protecting the privacy of children is VERY important to us. For that reason we do not structure any part of our site to attract anyone under the age of 18 (21 in some areas) and we do not allow anyone under the age of 18 (21 in some areas) to register and become a member of our site. 

HOW TO CANCEL YOUR SUBSCRIPTION  
You can cancel your subscription online by visiting the Customer Service section of the site you joined.

HOW CAN YOU CONTACT THE WEB SITE OPERATOR?  
Visitors who have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or their interactions with this Web site, can contact the website operator by sending an email to webmaster@magnusbucks.com.
